Contact

- Delhi, India 110091
- 8920038516
- rupak627@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rupak-chauhan-55909



Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS,

JavaScript

Database: PostgreSQL **Libraries:** jQuery, React Js

Cloud: AWS

OS: Ubuntu, Windows 10
Editors: Visual Studio Code,

Vim

UI Software: Adobe Photoshop

Version Control: Git

Courses

Udemy The Complete Web Developer Course 2.0:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, bootstrap, PHP, Python, MySQL & more!

Udemy Modern HTML & CSS (including Sass):

Modern responsive websites & Uls with HTML5, CSS3 & Sass! Also Flex & CSS Grid.

Udemy Introduction to Cloud Computing on Amazon AWS:



Sr. Customer Service Executive

I am a self-motivated professional with overall 3 years of mix experience in Web Development, Technical support and Customer Service.

I started my career with Tech Mahindra as Senior technical analyst in a US Telecom process

I now want to jump into Web Development and make a strong career out of it.

I am a strategic and analytic thinker, quick learner, with good interpersonal skills, like to have a "think outside the box" approach to address client's requirement. I like to learn new technologies regularly!

When I am not working, I like to go out for a walk, watch Ted talks, Netflix, or work out at gym.

Work History

2021-02 -Current

Sr. Customer Service Executive

lenergizer, Noida

- Responsible for attending customers' technical issues and resolving via emails.
- Providing billing related support over emails.

2021-10 -Current

Freelance Frontend Developer

Code Trays Information Technology Pvt. Ltd.

- Actively listened to customers' requests, confirming full understanding before addressing concerns.
- Prepared variety of different written communications, reports and documents.

2019-11 -2021-02

Sr. Technical Analyst

Tech Mahindra, Noida

 Responsible for attending customers' technical issues and resolving via chat. Developed hands— on S3, Route 53, AWS CLI, Auto-Scaling, Automation

Udemy The Complete
JavaScript Course 2021, From
Zero to Expert:

EC6, Parcel, Babel, async/await, functional programming

Udemy NodeJS with (MVC, REST APIs, GraphQL, Deno) -Udemy (In progress) Assists customers effectively by solving customer disputes. Provides customer with additional information or explains services.

Education

2016-08 -2019-08

BBA

IIMT Group of Colleges - Greater Noida

- Member of Debate Club
- Elected Captain of Sports Activities

2015-04 -2016-04

High School Diploma

Rishabh Public School - Delhi

- Awarded first prize in debate competition.
- Elected Captain of Athletics team